<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="DavisFall">
        "Davi\'s Falls is a waterfall located at"
        "Pokhara in Kaski District, Nepal."
        "Davi\'s Falls is a waterfall located at"
        "Pokhara in Kaski District, Nepal."
        "\n\nThe water forms an underground tunnel after reaching the"
        "bottom. This tunnel is approximately 500 feet (150 m) long and"
        "runs 100 feet below ground level. On 31 July 1961, a Swiss"
        "couple Davi went swimming but the woman drowned in a pit"
        "because of the overflow . Her body was recovered 3 days later in"
        "river Phusre with great effort. Her father wished to name it"
        ""Davi\'s falls" after her . Its Nepali name is Patale Chango, which"
        "means "underworld waterfall"."
        "\n\n"
        "After exiting the tunnel, the water passes through a cave called"
        "Gupteshwor Mahadev or "cave beneath the ground". The Phewa"
        "Lake dam is the water source."
        "\n\n"
        "It is an attraction for tourists and locals. Thousands of Nepalis"
        "visit for recreation and enjoyment. Visitors can try their luck on"
        "the luck pond constructed there by throwing and placing the coin"
        "on the statue of god. Likewise, one can find a model of"
        "traditional typical Nepali house and a series of statue of Nepali"
        "people wearing traditional dresses where visitors can click photo."
    </string>
    <string name="Sarangkot">
        "Sarangkot is a former Village Development Committee west"
        "of Pokhara in Kaski District Gandaki Zone. In 2015, it was"
        "annexed to Pokhara. At the time of the 1991 Nepal census it"
        "had a total population of 5,060 with 1,010 individual"
        "households."
        "\n\n"
        "The village is located on Sarangkot mountain at an altitude"
        "of 1600m and is renowned for its panoramic Himalayan"
        "views Dhaulagiri, Annapurna and Manaslu as well as down"
        "on the city of Pokhara and Phewa lake. In recent years,"
        "Sarangkot has become a hotspot for paragliding."
    </string>
    <string name="ShantiStupa">
        "Pokhara Shanti Stupa is a Buddhist pagoda-style monument on a hilltop in Ananda hill of the former Pumdi Bhumdi "
        "Village Development Committee, in the district of Kaski, Nepal (now a part of the city of Pokhara)."
        "\n\n"
        "Shanti Stupa in Pokhara was built by Nipponzan-Myōhōji monk Morioka Sonin with local supporters under the guidance of Nichidatsu "
        "Fujii, a Buddhist monk and the founder of Nipponzan-Myōhōji. Shanti is a Sanskrit word meaning peace, also widely used in Nepali and "
        "Hindi language, and Shanti Stupa means Peace Pagoda. Shanti Stupa is the shrine build as symbol of peace. The spot situated at the height "
        "of 1100 meters on the Ananda Hill was chosen by Nichidatsu Fujii and he laid the foundation stone as well with the relics of Buddha on the "
        "hilltop on 12 September 1973. Nepal has two of the eighty peace pagodas in the world: Shanti Stupa in Lumbini, the birthplace of "
        "Buddha and Shanti Stupa in Pokhara. Shanti Stupa in Pokhara has also become a tourist attraction. It provides a panoramic view of the "
        "Annapurna range, Pokhara city and the Fewa Lake."
        "\n\n"
        "Standing on top of the Ananda hill, Shanti Stupa adds more beauty to Pokhara Valley. It is a perfect holiday place providing a clear view of "
        "the Himalayan range, Fewa Lake and Pokhara city. The hilltop provides a splendid view of sunrise and sunset. TripAdvisor has ranked "
        "Shanti Stupa as top second attraction in Pokhara. The pagoda is 7 kilometers from Mahendrapool, the major business spot in Pokhara. "
        "There are several ways to reach the peace pagoda. There are hiking trails, cycling tracks and the blacked topped road to the Stupa. "
        "There are many trails for hiking. One of the popular and adventurous hiking trails is by crossing the Fewa Lake by a local boat and climb "
        "uphill through the local villages that takes about an hour to reach the hilltop. There have been cases of mugging in the hiking trails in "
        "previous years. The partial black-topped road from Chorepatan to the Stupa takes about 25 minutes, which can be reached by taxi or "
        "private cars. There is no public transports yet available to the foothill of the Stupa."
    </string>
    <string name="BegnasLake">
        "Begnas Lake is a freshwater lake in Lekhnath municipality"
        "of Kaski district of Nepal located in the south-east of the "
        "Pokhara Valley. The lake is the second largest, after Phewa"
        "lake, among the eight lakes in Pokhara Valley."
        "\n\n"
        "Water level in the lake fluctuates seasonally due to rain, and"
        "utilization for irrigation. The water level is regulated through"
        "a dam constructed in 1988 on the western outlet stream, Khudi Khola."
    </string>
    <string name="FewaLake">
        "Phewa Tal or Fewa Lake is a freshwater lake"
        "in Nepal located in the south of the Pokhara Valley that"
        "includes Pokhara city; parts of Sarangkot and Kaskikot. The"
        "lake is stream-fed but a dam regulates the water reserve,"
        "therefore, the lake is classified as semi-natural freshwater"
        "lake."
        "\n\nIt is the second largest lake in Nepal, the largest in"
        "Gandaki Zone followed by Begnas Lake."
        "Phewa lake is located at an altitude of 742 m (2,434 ft) and covers an area"
        "of about 5.23 sq km(2.0 sq mi)."
        "It has an average depth of about 8.6 m (28 ft) and "
        "a maximum depth of 24 m (79 ft)."
        "Maximum water capacity of the lake is approximately"
        "43,000,000 cubic metres (35,000 acre·ft)."
        "\n\nThe Annapurna range on the north is only about 28 km (linear distance)"
        "away from the lake. The lake is also famous for the"
        "reflection of mount Machhapuchhre and other mountain"
        "peaks of the Annapurna and Dhaulagiri ranges on its"
        "surface."
        "\n\nThe Taal Barahi Temple is situated on an island in the lake."
    </string>
    <string name="RupaLake">
        "Rupa Lake or Rupa Tal is a freshwater lake in Nepal located in the south-east of"
        "Pokhara valley that includes Lekhnath municipality.[1] It is the third biggest"
        "lake in Pokhara valley of Nepal and at an altitude of 600 m (1,969 ft) covering"
        "area about 1.35 km2 (0.5 sq mi) with an average water depth 3 m and"
        "maximum depth 6 m. The lake is elongated north to south and is fed by"
        "perennial streams. Its watershed area is 30 km²,[4] where The main inflow of"
        "water is from Talbesi stream, whereas Dhovan khola is the feeder stream with"
        "its outlet Tal khola at Sistani ghat. It supports a number of floral and faunal"
        "species. A total of 36 species of waterbirds have been recorded in the lake"
        "which represents about 19 percent of the total 193 wetland-dependent birds"
        "found in Nepal."
    </string>
    <string name="TalbarahiTemple">
        "Tal Barahi Temple, also known as Lake Temple or Barahi"
        "Temple is a two story pagoda temple located in the Kaski"
        " District of the Gandaki Zone in western Nepal."
        " It is a hindu temple of the Goddess Durga (Barahi), the protector of gods."
        " It is located in a small island on the south east section of Phewa Lake in Pokhara."
        " The temple is used for worship by both Hindus and Buddhists."
    </string>
    <string name="GupteshworCave">
        "Located close to Davis Falls"
        "on the other side of the World"
        "Peace Stupa the Gupteshwor"
        "Mahadev cave is Nepal' s"
        "most famous cave. It's also"
        "rumored to be the longest cave"
        "in Nepal  (2950 meters)."
        "The cave is said to be have"
        "been discovered in the 16th"
        "century. The main cave"
        "entrance was not constructed"
        "until 1991."
        "The main cave contains two"
        "chambers with several"
        "shrines located throughout."
        "The largest of these shrines is "
        "dedicated to Shiva. There is "
        "lighting in the cave that"
        "has a power back­up though "
        "bringing your own head torch is recommended."
    </string>
</resources>